flaticons.net 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - FlatIcons

Privacy policy 

Privacy of individual users 

FlatIcons.net does not require registration. Your use of this website does not identify you individually. FlatIcons.net uses third-party companies to collect and report detailed statistics about site use, but these statistics do not identify individual users, except to the extent that you may have provided this information to those companies. 

Cookies 

As is the case with almost all advertising-supported websites, FlatIcons.net uses browser cookie technology. A browser cookie is a small piece of data stored by a web server on your computer, to be read when you reconnect to that web server. FlatIcons.net includes third-party services which set and read browser cookies. Each third-party company has its own privacy policy. 

Google AdSense 

FlatIcons.net uses Google AdSense, a third-party advertising service operated by Google Inc., to serve ads when you visit FlatIcons.net. Google AdSense may use ["DoubleClick DART cookie"](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) technology to track information about your visits to FlatIcons.net and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that Google AdSense determines might be of interest to you. Google AdSense does not track your name, address, email address, or telephone number. If you would like more information about this practice, and to know your choices about not having this information used in this way, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Google Analytics 

FlatIcons.net uses Google Analytics, a third-party website analysis service operated by Google Inc., to collect and report detailed statistics about visits to FlatIcons.net. When you visit FlatIcons.net, Google Analytics servers automatically record and collect Log Data sent by your browser, including your computer’s IP address and the referring HTTP location. Google Analytics’ reporting is private. Google Analytics may place or read cookies. If you would like more information about cookies for Google Analytics, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and scroll to "How does Google use cookies for Google Analytics?" 

Server logs 

As is the usual case on web servers, each web transaction (request for HTML code and images) is recorded in a daily log file. This log file includes information such as your IP address, browser type, and operating system. The log does not include your name, address, email address, or telephone number. The log is used as input to produce reports of website statistics. 

Other 

FlatIcons.net reserves the right to add or remove third-party affiliate programs and other links, without updating this privacy statement. FlatIcons.net reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time without notice.
